let's check our understanding of and
module redundancy suppose we have a
computer and we want to tolerate faults
that can occur there so we go to a store
and buy two more computers just like the
first one and put all of them on the
same desk and our approach to redundancy
is that we run every computation on all
three computers we compare their outputs
and we take that output on which
two or all three agree and with this
approach we think we can tolerate any
single event of the following kinds
check each of those that can be
tolerated can we tolerate any single
alpha particle strike in a processor
can we tolerate any single building
collapse
can we tolerate any single earthquake
and can we tolerate any single mistake
in processor design